{
    "questions": [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is JavaScript primarily used for?",
        "choices": ["Styling webapges", "Making websites interactive", "Creating databases", "Generating server logs"],
        "answer": "Making websites interactive"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a variable?",
        "choices": ["var", "int", "string", "variable"],
        "answer": "var"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What will the follwing code output?  -$ console.log(2 + '2');",
        "choices": ["4", "22", "NaN", "undefined"],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which is the correct way to write a comment?",
        "choices": ["//Comment", "<!Commment>", "/* Comment */", "$$Comment" ],
        "answer": "//Comment"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What does NaN mean?",
        "choices": ["Null", "Negative number", "Not a number", "Network access number"],
        "answer": "Not a number"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which method is used to add an element to the end of an array?",
        "choices": [".add()", ".push()", ".pull()", ".unshift()"],
        "answer": ".push()"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which operator is used to compare two values for strict equality?",
        "choices": ["==", "!=", "===", "!=="],
        "answer": "==="
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "What is the purpose of the return statement?",
        "choices": ["It defines variables", "It returns to the previous page", "It loops through an array", "It exits the function and returns a value to the caller"],
        "answer": "It exits the function and returns a value to the caller"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which built-in object can be used to perform mathematical operations?",
        "choices": ["String", "Array", "Math", "Object"],
        "answer": "Math"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What is the correct way to write a 'for' loop statement?",
        "choices": ["for (let i = 0; i < 10; i++)", "for (i = 0; i < 10; i++)", "for (let i = 0)", "for (i < 10; i++)"],
        "answer": "for (let i = 0; i < 10; i++)"
    }
]
}